<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<DataFeeds>
    <item_data>
        <item_basic_data>
            <item_unique_id>B00VINDBJK</item_unique_id>
            <parent_asin>B011WESR1G</parent_asin>
            <item_ean_list>
                <item_ean_list_element>0848719069587</item_ean_list_element>
            </item_ean_list>
            <item_title>Kindle Oasis E-reader with Leather Charging Cover - Merlot, 6" High-Resolution Display (300 ppi), Wi-Fi - Includes Special Offers (Previous Generation - 8th)</item_title>
            <item_long_desc>&lt;div class="aplus"&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Unlike Any Kindle You've Ever Held&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Reimagined to be our thinnest and lightest Kindle ever&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt;New&lt;/b&gt;—Designed to feel as light as paper, Kindle Oasis is over 20% lighter and 30% thinner on average than any other Kindle. The handgrip tapers to an ultrathin 0.13" display so you can read comfortably for hours. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;b&gt;New&lt;/b&gt;—Kindle Oasis combines our strongest cover glass and a featherweight frame infused with metal using structural electroplating, ensuring it is lightweight while also resilient enough to take anywhere you want to read. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="leftImage"&gt;&lt;img alt="Kindle Oasis" src="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/G/01/kindle/dp/2016/10566252/mobile/kw-feature-ergonomic-design.jpg" width="100%"/&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Perfectly balanced ergonomic design&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt;New&lt;/b&gt;—A tapered ergonomic handgrip shifts the center of gravity to your palm, to rest in your hand like the spine of a book. Perfectly balanced for one-handed reading, Kindle Oasis enables you to get lost in your story. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;b&gt;New&lt;/b&gt;—Comfortably turn the page with either the touch display or dedicated page turn buttons located on the front of the handgrip. Whether you choose to read with your left or right hand, Kindle Oasis automatically rotates the page orientation to match. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Read More. Charge Less.&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Highest resolution Kindle with enhanced lighting&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt; Kindle Oasis features a high-resolution 300 ppi display for crisp, laser-quality text—all on the same 6" display size as Kindle Voyage. A redesigned built-in light features 60% more LEDs than any other Kindle, increasing the consistency and range of screen brightness for improved reading in all types of lighting. Kindle Oasis guides light toward the surface of the display with its built-in front light—unlike back-lit tablets that shine in your eyes—so you can read comfortably for hours without eyestrain. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Dual-battery charging system delivers months of battery life—our longest ever&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt;New&lt;/b&gt;—Charge the device and cover simultaneously while snapped together and plugged in. When on the go, the cover will automatically recharge the device, giving you months of combined battery life. Plus, a new hibernation mode minimizes power consumption when your Kindle is inactive, extending battery life to its fullest capacity. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Premium leather cover&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt;New&lt;/b&gt;—The removable charging cover is made of high-quality leather and comes in your choice of black, merlot, or walnut. The cover opens like a book and fits closely around the bezel, waking Kindle Oasis when opened and putting it to sleep when closed. Twelve magnets form a secure attachment between device and cover, while still easy to detach when the lightest possible weight is desired. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="leftImage"&gt;&lt;img alt="Kindle Oasis" src="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/G/01/kindle/dp/2016/10566252/mobile/kw-feature-read-more-device.jpg" width="100%"/&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;h4&gt;No glare in bright sunlight&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Unlike reflective tablet and smartphone screens, the micro-etched glass screen is crafted to eliminate glare and feel like paper to the touch. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Won't tire your eyes in the dark&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Kindle Oasis guides light toward the surface of the display with its built-in front light—so you can read comfortably without eyestrain. Adjust your screen's brightness for great reading in any light.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Charge monthly, not daily&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Kindle Oasis won't leave you tethered to an outlet. A single charge can last up to six weeks (based on a half hour of reading per day with wireless turned off and the light setting at ten).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="leftImage"&gt;&lt;img alt="Kindle Oasis" 
src="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/G/01/kindle/dp/2015/KM/Mobile/KM-mobile-DP-girl.jpg" width="100%"/&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Read comfortably with one hand&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Lighter than a paperback, comfortably hold Kindle Oasis in one hand for those times when you can't put the book down.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Lose yourself in a book&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;By design, Kindle Oasis is purpose-built for reading and creates a sanctuary so you can lose yourself in a book. Unlike tablets and phones, Kindle doesn't distract you with social media, emails, and text messages.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Take and share notes&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Add margin notes that you can edit, delete, or even export from your device to your computer. Share highlighted sections and meaningful quotes on Facebook, Twitter, and Goodreads, and see passages frequently highlighted by other Kindle readers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Look it up instantly without leaving your page&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Smart Lookup integrates entries from The New Oxford American Dictionary with information from X-Ray and Wikipedia, so you can access definitions, characters, settings, and more without losing your place.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Read more challenging books&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Word Wise makes it easier to enjoy and quickly understand more challenging books. Short and simple definitions automatically appear above difficult words, so you can keep reading with fewer interruptions. Tap on a word to bring up a simple card with definitions, synonyms, and more. Available on many popular English language titles.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Build your vocabulary&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Words looked up in the dictionary are automatically added to Vocabulary Builder to expand your knowledge and reinforce retention. Swipe through your vocabulary words, quiz yourself with flashcards, and instantly see those words in context.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Share your library&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;With Family Library, you and your family can access and easily share not only your own Kindle books, but also books from the linked Amazon account of a spouse or partner.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Lowest book prices, massive selection&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Over a million titles are priced at $2.99 or less. Over 2 million titles are $9.99 or less.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="leftImage"&gt;&lt;img alt="Kindle Oasis" src="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/G/01/kindle/dp/2015/KM/Mobile/KM-mobile-DP-kids.jpg" width="100%"/&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Set goals and celebrate with achievement badges&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Kids can read books in a simple, fun, and safe environment designed specifically for them with Kindle FreeTime. Kids are rewarded with achievement badges when they reach their reading milestones. A progress report keeps parents updated on total time spent reading, number of words looked up, badges earned, and books read.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;</item_long_desc>
            <book_size_description/>
            <item_page_url>http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00VINDBJK/ref=asc_df_B00VINDBJK5386849?tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=395261&amp;creativeASIN=B00VINDBJK&amp;linkCode=asn</item_page_url>
            <amzn_page_url>http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00VINDBJK/ref=asc_df_B00VINDBJK5386849/?tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=394997&amp;creativeASIN=B00VINDBJK&amp;linkCode=df0</amzn_page_url>
            <fm_page_url>http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00VINDBJK/ref=asc_df_B00VINDBJK5386849?smid=ATVPDKIKX0DER&amp;tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;linkCode=df0&amp;creative=395093&amp;creativeASIN=B00VINDBJK</fm_page_url>
            <offer_page_url>http://www.amazon.com/gp/offer-listing/B00VINDBJK/ref=asc_df_B00VINDBJK5386849?ie=UTF8&amp;condition=new&amp;tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=395165&amp;creativeASIN=B00VINDBJK&amp;linkCode=df2</offer_page_url>
            <offer_used_url>http://www.amazon.com/gp/offer-listing/B00VINDBJK/ref=asc_df_B00VINDBJK5386849?ie=UTF8&amp;condition=used&amp;tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=395213&amp;creativeASIN=B00VINDBJK&amp;linkCode=df2</offer_used_url>
            <tp_refurbished_url/>
            <tp_collect_url/>
            <tp_fba_url/>
            <item_image_url_small>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/514ZdtJAL5L._SL75_.jpg</item_image_url_small>
            <item_image_url>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/514ZdtJAL5L._SL160_.jpg</item_image_url>
            <item_image_url_large>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/514ZdtJAL5L.jpg</item_image_url_large>
            <item_image_url_hires>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/71Q7BHDSHcL.jpg</item_image_url_hires>
            <item_salesrank>557</item_salesrank>
            <list_price>289.99</list_price>
            <item_category>Amazon Ereaders</item_category>
            <item_is_fba>true</item_is_fba>
            <item_price>289.99</item_price>
            <item_inventory>Usually ships in 24 hours</item_inventory>
            <item_shipping_charge>0.00</item_shipping_charge>
            <item_condition>New</item_condition>
            <item_seller>Amazon.com</item_seller>
            <item_merchant_id>ATVPDKIKX0DER</item_merchant_id>
            <item_is_eligible_for_prime>1</item_is_eligible_for_prime>
            <item_sales_restriction>Check Site.</item_sales_restriction>
            <item_points/>
            <item_min_hours>0</item_min_hours>
            <item_max_hours>0</item_max_hours>
            <amzn_is_fba>true</amzn_is_fba>
            <amzn_price>289.99</amzn_price>
            <amzn_inventory>Usually ships in 24 hours</amzn_inventory>
            <amzn_shipping_charge>0.00</amzn_shipping_charge>
            <amzn_condition>New</amzn_condition>
            <amzn_seller>Amazon.com</amzn_seller>
            <amzn_merchant_id>ATVPDKIKX0DER</amzn_merchant_id>
            <amzn_is_eligible_for_prime>1</amzn_is_eligible_for_prime>
            <amzn_sales_restriction>Check Site.</amzn_sales_restriction>
            <amzn_points/>
            <amzn_min_hours>0</amzn_min_hours>
            <amzn_max_hours>0</amzn_max_hours>
            <fm_is_fba>true</fm_is_fba>
            <fm_price>289.99</fm_price>
            <fm_inventory>Usually ships in 24 hours</fm_inventory>
            <fm_shipping_charge>0.00</fm_shipping_charge>
            <fm_condition>New</fm_condition>
            <fm_seller>Amazon.com</fm_seller>
            <fm_merchant_id>ATVPDKIKX0DER</fm_merchant_id>
            <fm_is_eligible_for_prime>1</fm_is_eligible_for_prime>
            <fm_sales_restriction>Check Site.</fm_sales_restriction>
            <fm_points/>
            <fm_min_hours>0</fm_min_hours>
            <fm_max_hours>0</fm_max_hours>
            <tp_used_is_fba>false</tp_used_is_fba>
            <tp_used_price>169.99</tp_used_price>
            <tp_used_inventory>In Stock</tp_used_inventory>
            <tp_used_shipping_charge>Check Site.</tp_used_shipping_charge>
            <tp_used_condition>Used</tp_used_condition>
            <tp_used_seller/>
            <tp_used_merchant_id/>
            <tp_used_is_eligible_for_prime/>
            <tp_used_sales_restriction>Check Site.</tp_used_sales_restriction>
            <tp_used_points/>
            <tp_used_min_hours>0</tp_used_min_hours>
            <tp_used_max_hours>0</tp_used_max_hours>
            <item_sku/>
            <item_platform/>
            <item_is_adult_product/>
            <prototype_partner_product_id/>
            <amzn_ppu/>
            <tp_new_ppu/>
            <tp_used_ppu/>
            <tp_refurbished_ppu/>
            <tp_collect_ppu/>
            <item_energy_efficiency_class/>
            <item_abstract>Buy Kindle Oasis E-reader with Leather Charging Cover - Merlot, 6'' High-Resolution Display (300 ppi), Wi-Fi - Includes Special Offers (Previous Generation - 8th) from Amazon.com!</item_abstract>
            <weee_tax>0</weee_tax>
            <cpc/>
            <dcz/>
            <wxjz/>
            <xcyg/>
        </item_basic_data>
        <merch_cat_list>
            <merch_cat_item>
                <merch_cat_name>2642129011</merch_cat_name>
                <merch_cat_path>Electronics/Categories/eBook Readers &amp; Accessories/eBook Readers</merch_cat_path>
            </merch_cat_item>
            <merch_cat_item>
                <merch_cat_name>6669702011</merch_cat_name>
                <merch_cat_path>Amazon Devices &amp; Accessories/Categories/Amazon Devices/Kindle E-readers</merch_cat_path>
            </merch_cat_item>
        </merch_cat_list>
        <item_brand>Amazon</item_brand>
        <item_mpn_list>
            <item_mpn_list_element>B00VINDBJK</item_mpn_list_element>
            <item_mpn_list_element>53-003778</item_mpn_list_element>
            <item_mpn_list_element>SW56RW</item_mpn_list_element>
        </item_mpn_list>
        <item_upc_list>
            <item_upc_list_element>848719069587</item_upc_list_element>
        </item_upc_list>
        <item_features>Our thinnest and lightest Kindle ever--read even more comfortably for hours,All-new ergonomic design with dedicated buttons to effortlessly turn the page,Longest Kindle battery life--the included leather charging cover can boost battery to months. Choose from a black, merlot, or walnut removable cover.,High-resolution 300 ppi display with crisp, laser quality text. Reads like real paper without glare, even in direct sunlight.,Enhanced built-in adjustable light evenly illuminates the screen for perfect reading anywhere, anytime,Prime members read free with unlimited access to over a thousand titles</item_features>
        <item_part_number>B00VINDBJK</item_part_number>
        <item_package_quantity/>
    </item_data>
    <item_data>
        <item_basic_data>
            <item_unique_id>B00LG0QPIY</item_unique_id>
            <parent_asin>B00LG0QPIY</parent_asin>
            <item_ean_list/>
            <item_title>Kindle Fire HD 7", HD Display, Wi-Fi, 8 GB - Includes Special Offers</item_title>
            <item_long_desc>The new Kindle Fire HD is a full-featured HD tablet at an SD price. There's more to enjoy than ever before with a stunning HD display, faster performance, longer battery life, and lighter design  &lt;h4&gt; &lt;/h4&gt; &lt;div class="aplus"&gt; &lt;div class="leftImage"&gt;&lt;img alt="Kindle Fire HD" src="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/G/01/kindle/dp/2013/shared/mobile/tablet-mobile-soho_300._V350827340_.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Faster Performance&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Kindle Fire HD is over 60% faster than the previous generation Kindle Fire—a fast dual-core processor and an Imagination PowerVR 3D graphics core ensure games and video run smoothly. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Longer Battery Life&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;The Kindle Fire HD battery lasts longer than the previous generation Kindle Fire—up to 10 hours of reading, surfing the web on Wi-Fi, watching video, or listening to music. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Streamlined New Design&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Kindle Fire HD features a smaller bezel, cleaner lines, and optimized button placements. This all-new, streamlined design helps Kindle Fire HD disappear in your hands, so you can get lost in your viewing.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Custom Dolby Audio&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Kindle Fire HD uses the power of Dolby Digital Plus to create a world class audio experience. Kindle Fire HD is designed to automatically optimize the audio profile based on what you're doing (with or without headphones), such as watching a movie or listening to music.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;div class="leftImage"&gt;&lt;img alt="Kindle Freetime" src="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/G/01/kindle/dp/2013/shared/mobile/tablet-mobile-freetime_300.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Perfect for the entire family&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Kindle FreeTime is free on every new Kindle Fire. Parents can create a profile for each of their children and choose what books, apps, games, and videos they want to give their kids access to.  Parents can also set daily limits for tablet use, or restrict certain categories-like games and video-while leaving unlimited time for reading. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h4&gt;Stay connected&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;With every Kindle Fire you can stay connected with a cloud-optimized web browser, our new e-mail app and full social media integration. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Silk, a cloud-optimized web browser, is  faster and packed with new features like Reading View that removes all unnecessary images and other website clutter for a clean, easy-to-read version of the site. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The new e-mail app on Kindle Fire makes sending mail, viewing attachments, grouping conversations by subject, and syncing contacts simple and provides full support for popular e-mail providers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Kindle Fire tablets are fully integrated with Facebook and Twitter, making it easy to connect and share with friends and family. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="leftImage"&gt;&lt;img alt="Be entertained" src="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/G/01/kindle/dp/2013/shared/mobile/tablet-mobile-movies_300.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Be entertained&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt; Rent or purchase the biggest new releases and most popular titles from every major movie studio and TV network. Stream instantly over Wi-Fi or download to enjoy later. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Kindle Fire is built for the best in gaming, with tilt, turn, and multi-touch controls. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;See lyrics that display line by line while you listen to many of your favorite songs. You can also explore a more immersive artist experience with more photos, videos, and more. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Our interactive magazine experience allows you to start reading in just a few seconds with access to any back issue at any time on the cloud. All Kindle Magazines come with a 30-day free trial.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="leftImage"&gt;&lt;img alt="Be entertained" src="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/G/01/kindle/dp/2013/shared/mobile/tablet-mobile-productivity_300.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Get work done on Kindle&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Kindle Fire tablets provide a robust Exchange email  experience with ActiveSync, so you can check and reply to work e-mail  on-the-go. View Word, Excel, and PowerPoint files. Kindle Fire tablets also support  printing to your home or office's wireless printer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Compare Kindle Fire tablets&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;table class="data" width="240px"&gt; &lt;tbody&gt;  &lt;tr bgcolor="#eeeeee"&gt; &lt;td width="27%"&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td width="17%"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;small&gt;Kindle Fire HD&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td width="17%"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;small&gt;Kindle Fire HDX&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td width="23%"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;small&gt;Kindle Fire HDX 8.9"&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/td&gt;  &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt;   &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Starting Price&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt;   &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;$139&lt;/small&gt;   &lt;/td&gt;   &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;$229&lt;/small&gt;   &lt;/td&gt;   &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;$379&lt;/small&gt;   &lt;/td&gt;  &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr bgcolor="#eeeeee"&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Screen Size&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;7"&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;7"&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;8.9"&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt;  &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Resolution&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;1280 x 800&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;1920 x 1200&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;2560 x 1600&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt;  &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr bgcolor="#eeeeee"&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Processor&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Dual-Core 1.5 GHz&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Quad-Core 2.2 GHz&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Quad-Core 2.2 GHz&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt;  &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Battery Life&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;10 hrs mixed use&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;11 hrs mixed use&lt;br/&gt;   17 hrs reading&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;12 hrs mixed use&lt;br/&gt;   18 hrs reading&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt;  &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr bgcolor="#eeeeee"&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Audio&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Dolby Audio,&lt;br/&gt;   Dual Stereo Speakers&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Dolby Audio,&lt;br/&gt;   Dual stereo speakers,&lt;br/&gt;   Built-in microphone&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Dolby Audio,&lt;br/&gt;   Dual stereo speakers,&lt;br/&gt;   Built-in microphone&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt;  &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Wi-Fi&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Dual band Wi-Fi&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Dual band, dual antenna&lt;br /&gt; (MIMO) Wi-Fi&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Dual band, dual antenna&lt;br /&gt; (MIMO) Wi-Fi&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt;  &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr bgcolor="#eeeeee"&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;4G&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;None&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;4G Model Available&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;4G Model Available&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Camera&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;None&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Front-facing HD camera&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Front-facing HD camera&lt;br /&gt;   8 MP rear-facing camera&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt;  &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr bgcolor="#eeeeee"&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Storage&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;8 or 16GB&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;16, 32, or 64GB&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;16, 32, or 64GB&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt;  &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt;   &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Dimensions&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;7.5" x 5.0" x 0.42"&lt;/small&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;7.3" x 5.0" x 0.35"&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;9.1" x 6.2" x 0.31"&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt;   &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr bgcolor="#eeeeee"&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Weight&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;12.2 oz&lt;/small&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;10.7 oz&lt;br /&gt;     4G: 11.0 oz &lt;/small&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;13.2 oz &lt;br /&gt;   4G: 13.5 oz&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt;  &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Customer Support&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;Email, web, phone&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;small&gt;"Mayday" button +&lt;br /&gt;   email, web, phone&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;&lt;small&gt;"Mayday" button +&lt;br /&gt;   email, web, phone&lt;/small&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tbody&gt; &lt;/table&gt;  &lt;h4&gt;Technical details&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Display: 7" high definition touchscreen; 1280x800 resolution at 216 ppi, video playback up to 720p, with IPS (in-plane switching) technology, advanced polarizing filter, and anti-glare technology &lt;/li&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Size and Weight: 7.5" x 5.0" x 0.42" (191 mm x 128 mm x 10.6 mm).  12.2 ounces (345 grams). Actual size and weight may vary by configuration and manufacturing process&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;CPU &amp; RAM: 1.5GHz Dual-Core CPU, with 1GB of RAM&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Storage: 8GB (4.8GB available to user) or 16GB (11.9GB available to user) of internal storage&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Battery Life: Up to 10 hours of reading, surfing the web on Wi-Fi, watching video, or listening to music. Battery life will vary based on device settings, usage, and other factors such as web browsing and downloading content. Actual results may vary&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Charge Time: Fully charges in under 6 hours using the micro-USB power adapter included in the box, or slightly longer with other micro-USB power adapters that you may already have&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Wi-Fi Connectivity: Dual-band, single-antenna Wi-Fi. Supports public and private Wi-Fi networks or hotspots that use the 802.11a, 802.11b, 802.11g, or 802.11n standard with support for WEP, WPA, and WPA2 security using password authentication; does not support connecting to ad-hoc (or peer-to-peer) Wi-Fi networks&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Ports: USB 2.0 (micro-B connector) port for connection to a PC or Macintosh computer or to charge your device with the included power adapter&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Audio: 3.5 mm stereo jack and integrated stereo speakers with Dolby Digital Plus audio engine&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Content Formats Supported: Kindle (AZW), KF8, TXT, PDF, unprotected MOBI, PRC natively, Audible Enhanced format (AAX), DOC, DOCX, JPEG, GIF, PNG, BMP, Dolby Digital (AC-3), Dolby Digital Plus (E-AC-3), non-DRM AAC, MP3, MIDI, PCM/WAVE, OGG, WAV, M4V, MP4, AAC LC/LTP, HE-AACv1, HE-AACv2, MKV, AMR-NB, AMR-WB, HTML5, CSS3, 3GP, VP8 (WEBM)&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Sensors: Accelerometer, gyroscope&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Location Services: Location-based services via Wi-Fi&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Additional Features: External volume controls, built-in Bluetooth with support for A2DP compatible stereo headphones and speakers (no microphone support)&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Accessibility Features: Screen Reader, Explore by Touch, and Screen Magnifier, enabling access to the vast majority of Kindle Fire features. Screen Reader features IVONA's award-winning natural language text-to-speech voice. Also includes adjustable font sizes/color, and built-in Oxford dictionary.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;System Requirements: Kindle Fire HD is ready to use right out of the box—no setup, no software to install, no computer required to download content&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Warranty and Service: 1-year Limited Warranty and service included. Optional 2-year Extended Warranty available for U.S. customers sold separately.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Included in the Box: Kindle Fire 7" HD tablet, USB 2.0 cable, 5W power adapter, and Quick Start Guide&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
</item_long_desc>
            <book_size_description/>
            <item_page_url>http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00LG0QPIY/ref=asc_df_B00LG0QPIY5386849?tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=395261&amp;creativeASIN=B00LG0QPIY&amp;linkCode=asn</item_page_url>
            <amzn_page_url>http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00LG0QPIY/ref=asc_df_B00LG0QPIY5386849/?tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=394997&amp;creativeASIN=B00LG0QPIY&amp;linkCode=df0</amzn_page_url>
            <fm_page_url>http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00LG0QPIY/ref=asc_df_B00LG0QPIY5386849?smid=ATVPDKIKX0DER&amp;tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;linkCode=df0&amp;creative=395093&amp;creativeASIN=B00LG0QPIY</fm_page_url>
            <offer_page_url>http://www.amazon.com/gp/offer-listing/B00LG0QPIY/ref=asc_df_B00LG0QPIY5386849?ie=UTF8&amp;condition=new&amp;tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=395165&amp;creativeASIN=B00LG0QPIY&amp;linkCode=df2</offer_page_url>
            <offer_used_url>http://www.amazon.com/gp/offer-listing/B00LG0QPIY/ref=asc_df_B00LG0QPIY5386849?ie=UTF8&amp;condition=used&amp;tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=395213&amp;creativeASIN=B00LG0QPIY&amp;linkCode=df2</offer_used_url>
            <tp_refurbished_url/>
            <tp_collect_url/>
            <tp_fba_url/>
            <item_image_url_small/>
            <item_image_url/>
            <item_image_url_large/>
            <item_image_url_hires/>
            <item_salesrank/>
            <list_price>139.00</list_price>
            <item_category>Amazon Tablets</item_category>
            <item_is_fba>true</item_is_fba>
            <item_price>139.00</item_price>
            <item_inventory>Temporarily out of stock. Order now and we'll deliver when available. We'll e-mail you with an estimated delivery date as soon as we have more information. Your credit card will not be charged until we ship the item.</item_inventory>
            <item_shipping_charge>0.00</item_shipping_charge>
            <item_condition>New</item_condition>
            <item_seller>Amazon.com</item_seller>
            <item_merchant_id>ATVPDKIKX0DER</item_merchant_id>
            <item_is_eligible_for_prime>1</item_is_eligible_for_prime>
            <item_sales_restriction>Check Site.</item_sales_restriction>
            <item_points/>
            <item_min_hours>672</item_min_hours>
            <item_max_hours>1008</item_max_hours>
            <amzn_is_fba>true</amzn_is_fba>
            <amzn_price>139.00</amzn_price>
            <amzn_inventory>Temporarily out of stock. Order now and we'll deliver when available. We'll e-mail you with an estimated delivery date as soon as we have more information. Your credit card will not be charged until we ship the item.</amzn_inventory>
            <amzn_shipping_charge>0.00</amzn_shipping_charge>
            <amzn_condition>New</amzn_condition>
            <amzn_seller>Amazon.com</amzn_seller>
            <amzn_merchant_id>ATVPDKIKX0DER</amzn_merchant_id>
            <amzn_is_eligible_for_prime>1</amzn_is_eligible_for_prime>
            <amzn_sales_restriction>Check Site.</amzn_sales_restriction>
            <amzn_points/>
            <amzn_min_hours>672</amzn_min_hours>
            <amzn_max_hours>1008</amzn_max_hours>
            <fm_is_fba>true</fm_is_fba>
            <fm_price>139.00</fm_price>
            <fm_inventory>Temporarily out of stock. Order now and we'll deliver when available. We'll e-mail you with an estimated delivery date as soon as we have more information. Your credit card will not be charged until we ship the item.</fm_inventory>
            <fm_shipping_charge>0.00</fm_shipping_charge>
            <fm_condition>New</fm_condition>
            <fm_seller>Amazon.com</fm_seller>
            <fm_merchant_id>ATVPDKIKX0DER</fm_merchant_id>
            <fm_is_eligible_for_prime>1</fm_is_eligible_for_prime>
            <fm_sales_restriction>Check Site.</fm_sales_restriction>
            <fm_points/>
            <fm_min_hours>672</fm_min_hours>
            <fm_max_hours>1008</fm_max_hours>
            <item_sku/>
            <item_platform/>
            <item_is_adult_product/>
            <prototype_partner_product_id/>
            <amzn_ppu>139.00 / Item</amzn_ppu>
            <tp_new_ppu/>
            <tp_used_ppu/>
            <tp_refurbished_ppu/>
            <tp_collect_ppu/>
            <item_energy_efficiency_class/>
            <item_abstract>Buy Kindle Fire HD 7'', HD Display, Wi-Fi, 8 GB - Includes Special Offers from Amazon.com!</item_abstract>
            <weee_tax>0</weee_tax>
            <cpc/>
            <dcz/>
            <wxjz/>
            <xcyg/>
        </item_basic_data>
        <merch_cat_list>
            <merch_cat_item>
                <merch_cat_name>1232597011</merch_cat_name>
                <merch_cat_path>Electronics/Categories/Computers &amp; Accessories/Computers &amp; Tablets/Tablets</merch_cat_path>
            </merch_cat_item>
            <merch_cat_item>
                <merch_cat_name>6669703011</merch_cat_name>
                <merch_cat_path>Amazon Devices &amp; Accessories/Categories/Amazon Devices/Fire Tablets</merch_cat_path>
            </merch_cat_item>
        </merch_cat_list>
        <item_brand>Amazon</item_brand>
        <item_mpn_list>
            <item_mpn_list_element>53-000779</item_mpn_list_element>
        </item_mpn_list>
        <item_upc_list/>
        <item_features>1280x800 high definition LCD display with over one million pixels,Fast 1.5GHz dual-core processor,Ultra-fast web browsing over built-in Wi-Fi,Robust e-mail and calendar support for Gmail, Outlook, and more</item_features>
        <item_part_number/>
        <item_package_quantity>1</item_package_quantity>
    </item_data>
</DataFeeds>